<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tourist App</string>
    <string name="forgot_password"><u>Forgot Password?</u></string>
    <string name="not_registered"><u>Not Registered?</u></string>
    <string name="already_registered"><u>Already Registered?</u></string>

    <string name="light_sound_details">Step through a portal to ancient times, with the memorable Pyramids Sound and Light Show. The Sound Light show pyramids will take you on a journey thousands of years back, bringing the Egyptian legacy back to life! Thousands of years have passed since the pharaohs walked on earth, leaving behind a mystery on how the great pyramids were built. And, we can\'t just skip the enigmatic sphinx, standing prominently as a guard to protect the Great Pyramids.

With the Sound Light Show at the Giza pyramids, the pharaonic history is being re-told by the sphinx, unraveling the ancient secrets and mysterious tales. The Sound and Light show at the pyramids narrates the history of those great kings; Khufu, Khafre, and Menkaure. Choose between 10 different languages and get ready to hear this legacy! You can view the Sound and Light show schedule and check the pyramid timing and book Giza pyramids tickets online.</string>

    <string name="khufu_details">The Great Pyramid of Giza is the oldest and largest of the pyramids in the Giza pyramid complex bordering present-day Giza in Greater Cairo, Egypt. It is the oldest of the Seven Wonders of the Ancient World, and the only one to remain largely intact.</string>

    <string name="khafre_details">The Pyramid of Khafre or of Chephren is the second-tallest and second-largest of the 3 Ancient Egyptian Pyramids of Giza and the tomb of the Fourth-Dynasty pharaoh Khafre, who ruled c. 2558−2532 BC.</string>

    <string name="sphinx_details">The Great Sphinx of Giza, commonly referred to as the Sphinx of Giza, Great Sphinx or just the Sphinx, is a limestone statue of a reclining sphinx, a mythical creature with the head of a human, and the body of a lion.</string>

    <string name="khan_el_khalili_details">Khan el-Khalili is a famous bazaar and souq in the historic center of Cairo, Egypt. Established as a center of trade in the Mamluk era and named for one of its several historic caravanserais, the bazaar district has since become one of Cairo\'s main attractions for tourists and Egyptians alike</string>

    <string name="al_hakim_mosque_details">The Mosque of al-Hakim, nicknamed al-Anwar, is a major Islamic religious site in Cairo, Egypt. It is named after Al-Hakim bi-Amr Allah, the sixth Fatimid caliph and 16th Ismaili Imam. This mosque originally started being built by al-Aziz, the son of Mu\'izz, and the father of al Hakim, in 990 A.D.</string>

    <string name="beit_el_seheimy_details">Bayt Al-Suhaymi is an Islamic themed house and museum in Cairo, Egypt. It was originally built in 1648 by Abdel Wahab el Tablawy along the Darb al-Asfar, a very prestigious and expensive part of Islamic Cairo. In 1796 it was purchased by Sheikh Ahmed as-Suhaymi whose family held it for several subsequent generations.</string>

    <string name="baron_palace_details">Baron Empain\'s palace, with its Indian style, and its tower stands out in the desert landscape, is distinct from the rest of the city. The palace reflects the high status of its owner and marks a major milestone in the urban landscape of Heliopolis. Baron Empain\'s palace is the most prominent Monuments in the capital, its unique and innovative image attracting crowds of pedestrians on the road.

It was founded by Edward Louis Joseph Empain between 1907 and 1911. He was a Belgian businessman who was awarded the title "Baron" by the King of Belgium, on account of his economic contributions. The French architect Alexander Marcel was tasked with building this masterpiece.

The interior design of the palace consists of three floors topped by a roof. The palace is surrounded by a large garden from all sides. As for the basement, it contained a residence for the palace\'s servants, and consisted of a group of rooms connected by corridors and doors. The palace building is surrounded by a spiral staircase and an elevator that connects all the palace floors with a basement.
The ground floor consists of a reception room, a dining room, and a billiard room. As for the first floor, it houses four rooms, each with its own balcony and bathroom.  Finally, the roof of the palace comes as an open space on one of the sides of the tower, characteristic of the Baron Palace. </string>

</resources>